mediauk.com 2012-05-13

# Privacy Policy

_This was last updated February 2012. It reflects that we accept login by Facebook and Google, and how we store the information given; and that we now use Criteo for some advertising._

**Data Protection Act 1998 (UK)**   
This website is hosted in the UK, and run by [Not At All Bad Ltd](http://notatallbad.ltd.uk/). Not At All Bad Ltd is registered in the UK under the Data Protection Act 1998. Our registration number is Z1084808. Our Data Controller is James Cridland - you can contact him at james.cridland@mediauk.com. 

**Webservers and automatically-captured information**   
Not At All Bad Ltd runs www.mediauk.com. This website automatically collects information about which pages are visited, browsers used, the domain name (e.g., aol.com) of visitors, and information about where the user has come from. We use this to dynamically write the site so that it's relevant to you, and we also use it for internal review and for traffic audits. We use Google Analytics to assist us, who have a separate privacy policy: no personally-identifiable information is kept by Google Analytics. 

**Third party resources**   
Unlike many websites, we strive not to use third-party resources in our website. "Tweet this", "Facebook Like" and other snippets of code and images normally come from other websites, and, as a consequence, these companies know which pages you're looking at if it uses their code. We believe this is bad for your privacy; and accordingly, Media UK tries not to use third-party resources wherever possible. 

**Cookies**   
To help your surfing experience, this site uses cookies. Cookies are small files which help identify you to us when you ask for pages from our site. 

When you log in, we store a user-specific key inside a cookie ("muku"), so we know who we are. There is no personal information stored in this cookie: it's just a unique identifier for our database. It changes every time you log in. 

If you do not accept cookies, you can still passively use the site. This cookie is essential, however, if you want to log in. 

Google Analytics stores information in Media UK's cookie to assist in its analysis. 

**Email addresses and personal details**   
To passively use our site, we do not need any personal information. 

Some Media UK email services (like our jobs or news alerts) are activated through email. To use these services, you must supply us with a valid e-mail address: we check this is valid before using it. 

When logging in to our site, we get personal information from your account provider (currently Facebook or Google) about your name, email address, and other basic information, including a photograph where you have this set. We copy this information using a secure link between our website and theirs; and update it every time you log in. 

We may use the e-mail address you have given us to e-mail you important information regarding your account and new services by Media UK, not exceeding one e-mail a calendar month. These messages have a clear unsubscribe link where appropriate. 

When giving us feedback, in order for us to give you a reply we need your e-mail address. We also ask your name. Both of these pieces of information are not required. You should also know that your full e-mail address will not be seen by Media UK staff: only the site administrator has access. 

**Email lists, unsubscribing, and measures against spam**   
Media UK never sends [spam](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spam_%28electronic%29). 

Our daily email alerts and job postings all require a valid email address. You will be asked to check your email address and click on a URL we send you, or to log in via a third-party provider, to ensure you're posting from a valid email address and that you have access to that email address. This is called [confirmed opt-in](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Opt_in_e-mail), and universally recognised as best practice. 

Our daily email alerts come from alerts@mediauk.com and use the 'Precedence: bulk' mail header as recommended by Google. We want to make it easy to unsubscribe from these daily emails. Every one contains an unsubscribe link at the bottom, and further unsubscribe links in the List-Unsubscribe header, conforming with RFC2369. These trigger an 'unsubscribe' link in systems like Gmail and other email services. 

Our discussion alert emails come from admin@mediauk.com - we do not treat these as bulk mail. These have an unsubscribe link at the bottom of each message. 

To protect the health and reputation of our service, and ensure that all user details are correct, we monitor and agressively remove bouncing email addresses. If your email address bounces, your subscriptions to our email alerts, or discussion membership, may cease without warning or notification. 

While a UK company, we abide by the principles of the US 'CAN-SPAM' laws, and comply fully with the EU Privacy Directive 2002/58/EC. We do not give any of your information to any third party without your consent. 

Administrative emails come from admin@mediauk.com (or from personal accounts at mediauk.com's domain), including those that ask you to confirm your email address. 

**Release of personal details**

We do not give your details to any third party without your consent. 

However, by posting messages which could be considered as defamatory or libellous under English or European law, you are putting both yourselves and this website at risk. We reserve the right to release all available details to aid identification in case of legal action. We will not disclose them at any other time, and you will be notified if we wish to release them, and given every reasonable opportunity to settle the matter without recourse to release of information. 

YOU CANNOT USE THIS SITE TO POST LIBELLOUS, DEFAMATORY OR OTHERWISE ILLEGAL POSTINGS. 

**Advertising**   
Our advertising is supplied by Google AdSense and Criteo. Both companies use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit this website, and use cookies. These companies may use your visiting behaviour on this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you (rather than just giving you irrelevant advertising). 

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. You can read more about this, and opt out of this cookie, by visiting [Google's privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**Information held, and EU regulations**   
This website is hosted in the UK by Rackspace. Email to @mediauk.com is held on Google's email servers, which are both inside and outside the EU. Some feedback from the website is forwarded by email. 

**mediauk.net**   
The website at www.mediauk.net is governed by these privacy policies. All other services accessed through these pages have their own privacy policies which are linked clearly from all pages. 

**muk.fm**   
The short-link server at muk.fm is governed by these privacy policies. It uses no cookies, nor Google Analytics, and contains no advertising. This website automatically collects information about which pages are visited, browsers used, the domain name (e.g., aol.com) of visitors, and information about where the user has come from in the form of logfiles, which are regularly erased. 

***.mediauk.com and *.muk.fm**   
Subdomains of mediauk.com (except www.mediauk.com) and muk.fm are stored on Amazon S3 or Amazon Cloudfront, and are used to store static files. They use no cookies, nor Google Analytics. We do not maintain the logfiles on these domains. 

**Agreement**   
By using this site, you signify your assent to this policy, and also to our copyright restrictions. If you do not agree, please do not use the site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes.
